welcome brothers and sisters to another
Wednesday question and answer will we
open up with the Ten Commandments that
God commanded the whole world to keep
brother James yes sir and God spake all
these words saying I am the Lord thy God
which have brought thee out of the land
of Egypt out of the house of bondage
Thou shalt have nor the gods before me
thou sht not make unto thee any Graven
image or any likeness of anything that
is in heaven above or that is in the
earth beneath or that is in the water
under the Earth Thou shalt not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them for I the
Lord thy God am a jealous God visiting
the iniquity of the fathers upon the
children unto the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me and
showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord will not
hold him Guiltless that taketh his name
in vain remember the Sabbath day to keep
it holy six days shalt thou labor and do
all thy work but the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God in it Thou
shalt not do any work thou nor thy son
nor thy daughter thy manservant nor thy
maid servant nor thy cattle nor thy
strangers that are within that is within
thy gates for in six days the Lord made
Heaven and Earth the sea and all that in
them is and resteth the seventh day
wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day and hollowed it honor thy father and
thy mother that thy days may be long
upon the land which the Lord thy God
giveth thee Thou shalt not kill Thou
shalt not commit adultery Thou shalt not
steal Thou shalt not bear false witness
against thy neighbor Thou shalt not
covet thy neighbor's house Thou shalt
not covet thy neighbor's wife nor his
man's servant nor as maid servant nor as
Ox nor as ass nor anything that is thy
neighbors I've read Exodus 20: 1-1 17
may the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of this word in Jesus name we
pray amen am amen amen so he on question
and answer you can ask us a question and
we'll answer it according to the King
James Bible and if we cannot find the
answer we will seek further counsel to
bring you an answer at a later time the
questions we will not answer are the
vague long scripture questions and
questions of debate we're not here to
debate we are here to spread the true
Gospel of Jesus so please be as direct
as possible with your questions so we
can be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible no
other Bibles or books will be
acknowledged on this program also keep
in mind this is a live stream so feel
free to send in your questions that
pertain to Everlasting in life we just
asking that you keep them to a two
scripture maximum let me introduce to
you the family that's on the panel this
evening got brother Jerome Grace and
peace Brother Julius good evening
everybody brother Dre good evening
brother James good evening everyone
sister Deborah good evening brother
Sean good even we have and we have the
guest caller with us and I'm brother
Cornell sister deor what is our first
question of the evening yes there are
several held over questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's Q&A most love says I have
sinned in the past but asked for
forgiveness and repented I'm going
through some things how can I tell if
I'm getting Payback for the sins of my
past or if it's just trials and
tribulations well um if you repented and
been baptized in jesus' name then it's
not so much the past sins that it is
your trials and tribulations that you
might be going through right now let's
turn over to Psalms the 34th chapter
Psalms
34 because if you are walking with God
with all your heart and trying to do
this thing righteously and Psalms 34:19
applies to you as well as anybody else
that's trying to do what thus says the
Lord so when you get there brother read
that 34 and 19 for me go ahead many are
the afflictions of the righteous but the
Lord
deliverthat you going through right now
but the Lord say he'll deliver you out
of them all even so much that he said he
won't put more on you than you can bear
let's go to Hebrews the 12th chapter
Hebrews
12 when you get to that Hebrews
12 we're going to start at that verse
five Hebrews
12 and five because when we look at
trials and tribulations and afflictions
that you ask hey Jesus didn't commit one
sin and he went through
it pick it up at that verse 5 and go
ahead Hebrews 12
and5 and ye have forgotten exhortation
which speaketh unto you as unto children
my son despise not thou the chastening
of the Lord nor faint when thou art
rebuked of him so these words here take
heed to him don't forget these words of
of
exhortation go ahead for whom the Lord
loveth he chasteneth and scourgeth every
son whom he receiveth so the Lord whom
he love hey he chasteneth and scourgeth
and trials and tribulations come with
that too sometimes but hey the Lord love
you and you going through it that's not
a bad place to be go ahead if ye endure
chastening God dealth with you as with
sons for what son is he whom father
chasteneth not uhuh as well as daughters
go ahead but if ye be without
chastisement whereof are all or whereof
all are partakers then are ye bastards
and not Sons always better to be a son
than a bastard so if you going through
it right now and you know that you
serving the lord hey you're in a better
place than being a bastard where you
might be going through it and God ain't
even with you verse n furthermore for we
have had fathers of our flesh which
corrected us and we gave them reverence
shall we not much rather be in
subjection unto the father of spirits
and live uhhuh for they verily for a few
days chasen his us after their own
pleasure but he for our profit that we
might be partakers of his Hol yes
because sometimes you go through it you
know but um those that endure it to the
end and the same shall be saved so just
keep on running this race read the last
verse 11 now no chasing for the present
seeth to be joyous but Grievous
nevertheless afterward it yith the
Peaceable fruit of righteousness unto
them which are exercised thereby because
the Lord told us too that the trying of
our faith worketh patience so if you're
going through trials and tribulations
say hold on stay prayed up and the Lord
will bring a Deliverance to all those
who serve and Obey him that's all I
got all right we're gonna move on to our
next question hope that answered your
question sister debah moving on MC says
I have been giving to a lady I work with
for a year I never asked for anything
back I asked her one question when she
gets some extra money can I have at
least
$100 was I wrong to ask her that really
J
WR well we're going to let the um Bible
speak we're going to go to um Luke let's
go to St Luke chapter 6 and we going to
read verse
34 and
35 cuz it sounds like you uh you giving
her a gift
you
know she asked for some help and you and
you decided you wanted to help her okay
when you get it go ahead and read Luke 6
verse
34-35 and if ye lend to them of whom ye
hope to receive what think have ye for
Sinners also lend to Sinners to receive
as much
again but love ye your enemies and do
good and L
hoping for nothing again and your reward
shall be great and ye shall be the
children of the highest for he is kind
unto the unthankful and to the
evil now that's if you
lending and you you shouldn't hope for
anything back in return you know it's a
gift you know you trying to help them
you know but there's other there's
another situation just in case this if a
person is
borrowing from you and they ask for your
help and they borrowing from you that's
something a little different okay so if
you would say Hey you know I'mma borrow
$100 from you you know I'll pay you back
and of course you looking for the $100
back and if they don't want to pay you
back whatever reason they just don't
want to pay you back that's something
different okay so but it didn't sound
like your question was was about
somebody borrowing from you but let's
address the borrowing situation anyway
let's go to Psalms
37 and read one verse verse
21 okay Psalms 37 and verse 21
says the wicked Borth and payeth not
again but the righteous showeth mercy
and giveth yeah so even in that case if
they don't pay back
okay the Bible say the wicked pay not
back but you still as a servant of the
Lord you still going to show some mercy
okay that's all I got
him all right thank you for that brother
better to give than to receive all right
we're going to move on to our next
question next question Cynthia Peterson
States in Hebrews 8
verse1 it says we should no longer be
teaching each other in the New Covenant
so why are we still teaching our
neighbors all right why don't we go to
Hebrews 8 and
11 and they want to deal with this
teaching our neighbor and the guest
caller would take it from there Hebrews
8 and
11 okay Hebrews 8 And1 says and they
shall not teach every man his neighbor
and every man his brother saying know
the Lord For All Shall know me from the
least to the
greatest now let's back up uh uh verse
10 and read it okay verse 10 says for
this is the Covenant that I will make
with the house of Israel after those
days sayeth the Lord I will put my laws
into their mind and write them in their
hearts and I will be to them a God and
they shall to me a
people now the first thing is he have to
put his laws in your heart now if his
laws is not in your heart then you
that's your mind then you have to be
taught why is that let's go quickly to
119th chapter of Psalm and read verse
11 okay see what is written here 119 and
ver Psalm 119 and verse 11 says Thy word
have I hi in my heart that I might not
sin against
thee see the first thing is to keep
people from sin against God you have to
put the word in their heart in other and
the only way for you to put in in that's
their mind is to teach them but people
use this to say that we have we are not
under the New Covenant but no the
Covenant didn't come like that the Lord
the New Covenant let me let me show you
when when the New Covenant started
because uh this conversation is is is
wide me we're not under the New Covenant
because we still have to teach people
let's go to Hebrews the 10th
chapter we're going to read verse one
then we're going to skip down and read
ver verse 5 through 10 okay after that
14 through 17 verse one Hebrews 10 And1
Hebrews 10:1 says for the law having a
shadow of good things to come and not
the very image of those things of the
things can never with those sacrifices
which they offered year by year
continually make the comers there unto
perfect now why couldn't it skip down to
verse five and
continue verse five says wherefore when
he cometh into the world he saith
sacrifice and offering thou wouldest not
but a body has has thou prepared me and
backe back up to uh uhh verse four first
okay verse four verse four says for it
is not possible that the blood of bulls
and of goats should take away
sins so now the book animal sacrifice
was under the old Covenant and they
couldn't take away sin so Jesus said a
body had thou prepared me he needed this
body for a reason verse five read verse
five again wherefore when he cometh into
the world he saith sacrifice and
offering thou wouldest not but a body
has thou prepared me go ahead and burnt
offerings and sacrifices for sin thou
has had no
pleasure then then said I lo I come in
the volume of the book it is written of
me to do thy will oh God so he come it
is written of him to come and die for
the sins of the people but go ahead
above when he said sacrifice an offering
and burnt offerings an offering for sin
thou wouldest not neither has pleasure
therein which are offered by the
law go ahead then he said then said he
lo I come to do thy will oh God he
taketh away the first that he may
establish the second now see Jesus came
and he took away the first that he may
establish the second but how did he take
away the first Covenant
read it by the which will we are
Sanctified through the offering of the
body of Jesus Christ once for
all so now when Jesus died on the cross
that's set that that's set in order the
New Covenant skip down to verse 14 and
read the 17 go ahead for by one offering
he have perfected forever them that are
Sanctified whereof the Holy Ghost ghost
also is a witness to us for after that
he had said before this is the Covenant
I will make with them after those days
sayeth the Lord I will put my laws into
their hearts and in their minds will I
write them and their sins and iniquities
will I remember no
more so the first thing he had to do is
he had to set up a covenant for them to
become a part of because a government a
covenant is a is a uh uh uh
uh is is an agreement standing between
uh uh you know two entities so people
think that the Covenant had to be uh the
Covenant uh uh started won't start until
you don't have to teach anybody but the
Covenant was already started when Jesus
died on the cross that's why some put in
your heart but now you have to be
brought into this Covenant and let's
look at this Covenant let's let's go to
Z and look at what what uh what
Zechariah the 9th chapter say Zechariah
and9 and Skip to verse
11 okay Zechariah 9 and9 says Rejoice
greatly oh Daughter of Zion shout oh
daughter of Jerusalem Behold thy King
cometh unto thee he is just and having
salvation lowly and writing upon an ass
and upon upon a coat the F of an
ass vers 11 what he
did as for thee also as for thee also by
the blood of thy Covenant I have sent
forth thy prisoners out of the pit
wherein is no
water so now when Jesus died the New
Covenant had been set in order but it's
up to each individual to come and be
come a part of that Covenant let's go
into Hebrews the 9th chapter Now read
verses
16-8 I'm take a little on this because I
know what a mind say is verse 16 and 18
go ahead Hebrews 9 And1 16-18 says for
where a testament is there must also of
necessity be the death of the testator
for a testament is of force after men
are dead otherwise it is of no strength
at all while the testator liveth
whereupon neither the first testament
was dedicated without blood
now see the The Testament means Covenant
so in order
for Covenant be put in force the one
that the covenant made us be dead even
like the old Covenant when when it when
it was instituted it was instituted by
Blood but Moses didn't die he used
animals let's go into
Exodus the 24th chapter read verses
4-8 let you know how the old C Testament
was sitting on go ahead okay Exodus 24
4-8 says and Moses wrote all the words
of the Lord and Rose up early in the
morning and builded an altar upon under
the hill and 12 pillars according to the
12 tribes of Israel and he sent young
men of the children of Israel which
offered burnt offerings and sacrificed
peace offerings of oxen unto the Lord
and Moses took half of the blood and put
it in basins and half of the blood he
sprinkled on the Altar and he took the
book of the Covenant and read in the
audience of the people and they said all
that the Lord has said will we do and be
obedient and Moses took the blood and
sprinkled it
listen got he got the the words of the
Covenant and he read the book to these
people and they said all that the Lord
said
we will do so we had to hear it first
but go ahead and read verse 8 says and
Moses took the blood and sprinkled it on
the people and said behold the blood of
the Covenant which the Lord ha made with
you concerning all these
words okay so now the New
Covenant is already established when
Jesus died on the
cross but in order for you to uh uh be a
part of that Covenant you have to come
under the blood of that Covenant and you
have to do that by baptism so once you
are taught and told what you have to do
then nobody your neighbor and your
neighbor then you don't have to teach
them anymore cuz they know but as far as
the other people come in how can you
come under a covenant you don't know the
terms of the Covenant you don't even
know you have to be baptized in the name
of Jesus to be a part of that
Covenant because he is the mediator of
the New Covenant so the COV in forced it
was in forced since he died on the cross
so now all this is saying is that once
you come into that Covenant when you
come into it that means somebody been
told you what it is what you doing that
mean you've been taught now nobody have
to teach you
anymore but somebody have to teach the
other one the other people that don't
know about the Covenant but the Covenant
is not is it will it will not be people
saying that well you know everybody have
to know the Lord the Lord no you don't
the one that's under the Covenant is the
one that you teach once you teach that
person you don't have to teach that
person no more once you teach that
neighbor then you don't have to teach
that neighbor no more but for the next
person that don't know the terms of the
Covenant you have to teach that's all
it's saying don't have nothing to do
with the existence of the Covenant it
has something to do with you coming in
coming into it
because just like Moses sprinkled of
blood on all Israel Jesus did the same
thing but you have to do what the Lord
say the Covenant is in force that's all
I have to
say can I accept some man should got me
all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
next one commissioner Paula a Sanford
says there are no iog or Sabbath keeping
class Church in my new city my
granddaughter wants to find a church to
attend I'm not sure where she should go
suggestions well you you didn't um leave
us any idea where your new city is at
because we do have churches spread all
around but we have no idea where you at
so um you can either resubmit where you
at or we also have a phone number that
you can call doing business hours 708
1320 and you can let them know what city
you in and they should be able to be of
assistance to let you know whether or
not there's something in that area of
your new
city and that's all I got on
thatl yes sir go ahead I say one thing
concerning that then you keep your
granddaughter if you can't find one keep
them watching it on uh on the Internet
or YouTube right because if you going to
go to church that's uh if she want take
her to a church that's Pagan you're not
doing your granddaughter no good you are
destroying
her that's all I have to
say all right hope that ansed your
question as we move on to our next one
moving on Elizabeth cochell says what's
scriptures will one try and use to say
we are Gentiles they try and use if
you're not a Jew you're a
gentile all right brother Julius we know
some people even teach that we are
Gentiles what you say brother let's look
at the book said we have a more sure
word of of Prophecy let's go back and
look at what the prophets wrote let's go
to Moses let's show you the definition
of a
gentile Genesis chapter 10 brother
because that is a myth if you're not a
Jew then you are Gentiles let's see who
let's see the sons of Noah who populated
this whole earth Genesis 10 and one go
ahead now these are the generations of
the sons of Noah shim ham and japheth
and unto them were Sons born After the
flood now to them were Sons born After
the flood and he'll tell you
you that out of Noah's three sons was
the whole earth overspread go ahead
verse two the sons of japat Goomer and
Magog and Mida and Javan and tubal and
meach and Tyrus and the sons of goer
ashkenaz and riab and togar and the sons
of Javan El Elisha and Tarsus Kum and
dodanim by these were the a of the
Gentiles divided in their lands everyone
after his tongue after their families
and their Nations now
now uh these are Europeans or what we
call white folks or Caucasians and their
descendants
okay white folks Europeans and their
descendants now let's go and look at a
scripture that they try to use
that well they try to let's go to
Matthew the 4th chapter which is really
a
prophecy well before we get there James
whole hold Matthew let's go to Isaiah
the nth chapter because this is one
place that I found it that people try to
use this somebody try to use this on
me Isaiah 9 and pick it up at verse one
let's pay attention to the words that
we're listening to and reading go ahead
nevertheless the den shall not be such
as was in her vexation when at the first
he lightly Afflicted the land of zabulon
and the land of Nepali and afterward did
more grievously afflict her by the way
of the sea Beyond Jordan and Galilee of
the Nations and Galilee of the Nations
but we got two tribes that are named
here of the tri of the House of Israel
right now let's go to Matthew the 4th
chapter
okay Matthew 4 and this kind we going to
pick it up at verse 12 now this was a
prophecy when Jesus would come on the
scene but remember Galilee of the
Nations because that's the holy land
now Matthew 4 and pick it up at verse 12
when you get it James go ahead now when
Jesus had heard that John was cast into
prison he departed into Galilee go ahead
and and leaving Nazareth Nazareth the
town where he was brought up he was born
in Bethlehem but he was raised up in
Nazareth which is in Israel go ahead he
came and dwelt in Capernaum which is
upon the Sea Coast in the borders of
zabulon and NEP talum those are those
are the two Nations that we just read
about in Isaiah the 9th chapter to
fulfill scripture go ahead that it might
be fulfilled which was spoken by Isaiah
the prophet saying the land of zabulon
and the land of nepalm by the way of the
sea Beyond Jordan Galilee of the
Gentiles so now this is what they try to
use that says the land of Israel the
Gentiles no the Gentiles occupied that
because the Romans were ruling the world
and still ruling the world as a whole uh
that area the Romans ruled that world
and the Romans are Gentiles of the
children of japheth so it is a lie that
you that if you're not a Jew that you
are a gentile because on your own go
back to Genesis the 10th chapter and you
can pick up Noah's son Ham you're
African peoples because the book said by
these three sons was the whole earth
overspread so it is a myth that if
you're not a Jew then you are a gentile
you are a gentile if your father or your
bloodline come through the children of
japet or the
Caucasus that's all I got anybody else
want to comment on that
all right I'm we leave it right there
hope that answered your question as we
move on to our next moving on Valencia
ask for you to explain what does letter
rain mean in James 5 verse
7 all right what does the the Latter Day
Rain what does that mean in that James 5
and 7 Dre what you say let's go to James
5 and7 and read it brother when you get
it go ahead
James 5:7 says be patient therefore
Brethren unto the coming of the Lord
behold the husbandman waiteth for the
precious fruit of the earth and have
long patience for it until he receiveth
the early and latter
rain read verse eight be ye also patient
establish your hearts for the coming of
the Lord draweth not okay so so he is
saying be patient therefore Brethren
onto the coming of the Lord then he
gives you an example he said behold the
husband man waiteth for the precious
fruit of the earth and have long
patience for it until he receive the
early and the latter rain which is what
the farmer does and then he reaps his
Harvest let's go look at that let's go
to Deuteronomy
11 Deuteronomy 11 and we're going to
read vers 13 and
14 okay Deuteronomy 11 and vers 13 and
14 say and it shall come to pass if ye
shall hearken diligently unto my
Commandments which I command you this
day to love the Lord your God and to
serve him with all your heart and with
all your soul that I will give you the
rain of your land in its due season the
first rain and the latter rain that thou
mayest Gather in thy corn and thy wine
and thine oil so he's just saying as an
example you be patient onto the coming
of the Lord just like the husband man is
patient and he looks for the latter rain
and and the early rain and the latter
rain so it's just talk talking about how
the
farmer looks for that
rain that the Lord brings to give his
Harvest and he promises that if you do
what he tell you to do he will give it
to you so just be patient that's what he
say that's all right thank you for that
brother hope that answer that question
as we move on to our next moving on
rodri Durham States the safety place
during the Great Tribulation in the
Third Temple he asked did your teacher
teach you this or by the grace of God
through scriptures he revealed it to
you all right guess caller what you
say my teacher told me that and I read
some book
too so that's the order of things Jesus
said everything in order because he did
it with the prophets I want you to go
quickly and
read Matthews the uh uh uh 28th chapter
just want look at something right
quick let's say
uh in verse 19
2819 okay Matthew 2819 says go ye
therefore and teach All Nations
baptizing them in the name of the father
and the name and the uh of the son and
of the Holy
Ghost okay the thing I went there is for
is go
ye all uh uh go ye teaching all the
nations see just like uh just like uh uh
we learn and I learned about uh uh about
the Wilderness and where it's going to
be I had to be taught that is the order
of thing the Lord set it in order and
the Lord said this go into Jeremiah 3:5
Look What the Lord
say Jeremiah 3 and 15
says and I will bring and I'm sorry and
I will give you pastors according to my
heart which shall feed you with the
knowledge and
understanding so you get men from God
pastors and teachers the Lord sent them
and uh uh and they G and they feed you
with knowledge and understanding the
Lord work that way let's go into acts
the 8th chapter and read verse
26-31 Acts the 8th chapter vers
to I'm
sorry 26 26 to 31 so Acts 8: 26-31 says
and the angel of the Lord spake unto
Phillip saying arise and go toward the
South unto the way that goeth down from
Jerusalem unto Gaza which is
Desert and he rose and went and behold a
man of Ethiopia a unic of great
Authority Under Candice queen of
Ethiopians of the Ethiopians who had the
charge of all her treasure and had come
to Jerusalem for to worship was
returning and sitting in his Chariot
read Isaiah the
prophet uhuh then the spirit said unto
Phillip go near and join thyself to this
Chariot and Philip ran thither to him
and heard him read the prophet Isaiah
and said understandest thou what thou
readest and he
said he asked him a question understand
do you understand understand what you're
reading and what did he say and he said
how can I accept some man should guide
me and he des and
he read that different read it again and
and he said how can I except some man
should guide me that's what I'm looking
for how can I except some man shall
guide me and and guide him through what
through the scriptures
go to one last place Isaiah the 8th
chapter read verse 9 and
10 Isaiah the 8th
chapter Isaiah 8 vers 9 and 10 say
associate yourselves oh ye people and ye
shall be broken in pieces and give
ear Isaiah 28 I'm sorry okay not a
problem Isaiah
20 Isaiah 28:9 and 10 says Whom Shall he
teach knowledge and Whom Shall he pay
attention to how you started out Whom
Shall he teach
knowledge Whom Shall he teach knowledge
now go ahead and Whom Shall he make to
understand Doctrine and Whom Shall he
make to understand Doctrine that's
something that's written go ahead them
that are lean from the milk and drawn
from the
breast go ahead for precept must be upon
precept precept upon precept line upon
line line upon line here a little and
there a
little so that's how I was taught a man
taught me but he taught me by way of the
scripture all that simple I had had no
special holy ghost in my head that
guided me I had a man that taught me and
he used the scripture that to teach me
and he used that same method when he
showed me taught me and others where the
place of safety was going to be that's
all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question there we move on to our next
question next question time out Houston
says I need to understand are the laws
in Deuteronomy 22 verse1 about mixed
fabrics and Leviticus 19 verse 27 about
not cutting hair still required
today all right so brother James let's
go to Deuteronomy 22
And1 and that's going to be dealing with
the fabrics and they also got some of
our cutting the hair in Leviticus 19- 27
but Deuteronomy 22 and11 and the guest
caller will take it from there okay
Deuteronomy 22 and11 says Thou shalt not
wear a garment of diverse sorts as of
wool Woolen and linen
together now the first thing is they
talking at uh uh uh not mixing certain
Fabrics together
but I want you to read the other one now
okay and Leviticus 19 and 27 says ye
shall not round the corners of your
heads neither shalt thou Mar the corners
of thy
beard now I'm reading both of
these but I notied something first thing
is I didn't see nowhere where the Lord
said these are it is a sin to do
these so I don't know I don't know what
the uh uh What uh uh around the corners
of the build is I don't know but I do
know but I know one thing that's how to
get eternal life let's go and look at
that let's go into Matthew the 19th
Chapter
and let's
see 19 and the
uh
verse
16 okay
17 so so would you like for me to read
uh 16 and
17 yes chapter 19 vers 16 and 17 okay
Matthew 19 and verse 16 says and behold
one came and said unto him good Master
what good things shall I
do goad that I may have eternal
life specific what good thing shall I do
that I might have eternal life go ahead
and read and he said unto him why
callest thou me good there is none good
but one that is God but if thou will
enter into life keep the
commandments so now I don't know about
the mix uh clothing whether it's in forc
or not and I don't know what cutting off
the corner of the beard is but I do one
thing do know one thing according to
what Jesus said if you want to get
eternal life you better keep the
Commandments that's all that say that is
for
sure all right hope that answered your
question there and as we move on to our
next uh next question Barbara still asks
where in the Bible does this say God and
Jesus Took sweet counsel
together godhead took sweet counsel
together the master plan of God for
everything that was
created all right let's go into Psalms
the 55th
chapter and let's pick it up at that
verse
13 this will be talking about the
godhead and then we'll go straight into
they question about where does it say
that they took sweet counsel together go
ahead brother but it was thou a man mine
equal mine guy and mine
acquaintance we we took sweet counsel
together and walked into the house of
God in company yep and they took sweet
counsel to together and walked unto the
house of God in company and are sitting
on Thrones right now so thank God for
that Master Plan when they took that
sweet counsel together to even save us
from ourselves that's all I
got and we hope that that answers your
question as we move on to our next
question with the time
check yes
the time is
8:14 and um Julia um D Mar King
says how are we supposed to understand
Jesus being God if the Old Testament
says God is not a
man in Hosea
11:9 and not the son of man in numbers
23 verse
19 all right brother Julius share some
light on that question there you know I
I was looking at this question I was
looking at this question and somebody
don't believe or understand the
book sometime we try we look at similar
scriptures and then we try to uh make
them connect and they don't always
connect we could be talking about two
different subjects let's see if we can
straighten this out let's go to Hosea
James 11
I'm there Hosea 11 and let's read this
scripture 11 and
N because the Lord made a covenant with
Israel he will not break it he will keep
it he will keep it men break covenants
God don't break
covenants okay men can lie God it's
impossible for God to lie and we can
read that 11 and9 go ahead I will not
execute the fierceness of mine anger I
will not return to the to destroy
Ephraim for I am God and not man the
Holy One in the midst of thee and I will
not enter into the city so God is a
covenant God if you read verse eight he
will tell you how should I give you up
verse one tell you Israel when Israel
was a child he made this Covenant
Abraham Isaac and Jacob and his seed
after him he will keep his Covenant he
is not going to give them up God he uh
he said for I am God he's almighty God
with all power and not man because men
don't have the power that God have and
God cannot lie that's why it said for I
am God and not
man now let's go to numbers the 23rd
chapter I'm there numbers
23 and when you get there pick it
up read that verse 20
19 God is not a man uhhuh that he should
lie see there God is not a man that he
should lie go ahead neither the son of
man that he should repent and he don't
have to
repent he don't have to repent he can if
you want to but he don't have to man lie
and when man lie man must repent to have
forgiveness of that finish it up broath
he said have he said and shall he not do
it yeah go ahead or have or have he
spoken and shall he not make it good so
everything that the Lord wanted us to
know he put it in his book it has
happened it will happen so therefore
sisters and brothers God is not a man
that he should lie neither the son of
man that he should repent he don't have
to
repent man have to do all that so we're
putting a difference between God who has
all power and man who dies get old
wrinkled so on and so forth and lie and
God ain't none of that he's perfect I
hope that helped can I add a little
something brother Julius I wanted to add
First Timothy 3 and 16 absolutely and it
kind of tie into that uh St John 1
one and
two you know yeah he left from being God
and he took on flesh yeah to die for the
sins of man so you
know read that 1 Timothy
3:16 1 Timothy 3:16 Says and without
controversy great is the mystery of
godliness God was manifest In the Flesh
justified in the spirit seen of Angels
preached unto the Gentiles believed on
in the world received up into Glory he
said now he asked the father I don't
finish the work you sent me to do now in
this Flesh and Blood he said now give me
the glory which I had with thee before
the world was that's right that's John
17 yes sir and then John 4 24 tell you
God is a
spirit his flesh
let's let's go and look at something
here let's go to
Hebrews yes that's right that body was
prepared Hebrews chapter
2 and uh we going to uh uh we just going
to start uh showing you what happened
start at verse n 2 and N okay Hebrews 2
and9 says but we see Jesus who was made
a little lower than the angels for the
suffering of
death crowned crowned with glory
and we had to have a sin offering Jesus
was God so in order for him to uh uh die
for the sins of the people because they
couldn't find a man that was worthy
Hebrews the 10th chapter tell you that
the father prepared him a body that's
Hebrews 10
5-7 so so you made the Lord and Angel
for Ser of death go ahead crowned with
Glory and Honor that he by the grace of
God should taste death for every man
amen now then and and pay attention to
this 10th verse
here for it became him for whom are all
things and by whom are all things and
bringing many
son here for it became him for whom are
all
[Music]
and by whom are all things that mean he
made everything right that's right yes
and bringing many sons unto glory to
make the captain of their salvation
perfect through
sufferings read for both he that
sanctifieth and they whom are Sanctified
are all of one for which cause he is not
ashamed to call them
Brethren okay then
skip down to verse
14 verse 14 says for as much then as the
children are partakers of Flesh and
Blood he also himself likewise took part
of the same that through death so he was
not flesh and blood in the
beginning so what he did was for the
children of flesh and blood so he also
but took the same in other words
he is the one that took part in Flesh
and Blood became that but go ahead that
for what reason that through death he
might destroy him that had the power of
death that is the
devil and deliver them who through fear
of death were all their lifetime subject
to
bondage for verily he took not on him
the nature of angels but he took on him
the Seed of
Abraham now when he did
that then he was
man he wasn't God at the time he was man
right that's why when the young fell
asked him what should I do good Master
what should I do to get eternal life he
said why callest thou me good right only
God is good but if you will enter into
life keep the Commandments
so Jesus when he became flesh and blood
when the body was made for him Angel
putting in Mary he had it then Jesus
himself called himself the son of man
yes so he man and he called himself the
son of
man so now Jesus said who going to
dispute
it
nobody that's all I have to say all
right hope that answered your question
as we continue to move to our next
question moving on bear of word added to
Israel states there is often said that
the only angels in the Bible that have
names are Michael Gabriel and Lucifer
but what about death and hell in
Revelation 6: 7 and 8 notice how they
are capit to Li aren't those angels too
these will be cast in the lake of fire
with Satan in Revelation 20
verse4 all right
so they asking about some names and
trying to tie to death and hell and make
them angels and we're gonna see what the
guest caller got to say about that let's
go to Revelation
6 and they want to pick it up as uh
verse seven and 8 and then the guess T
would take it from
there
okay Revelation 6 verse 7 and8 says and
when he had opened the fourth seal I
heard the voice of the fourth Beast say
come and see and I looked and behold a
Pale Horse and him his name that set on
him was death and Hell Followed after
mean followed with him and power was
given unto them over the the fourth part
of the earth to kill with the sword and
with hunger and with death and with the
Beast of the
earth
death is when one dies that is not an
angel and hell is the grave the other
word for that is shuel so once Jesus
terminated death then there was no more
death and if nobody died there was was
no need for a grave so it's a metaphor
when he said that death and hell was
cast into the L of fire all he saying is
he terminated
death let's go to First Corinthians 15th
chapter
okay and and uh uh let's see where we're
going to started
at 15
and U start reading at verse
21 okay 1 Corinthians 15 and in verse 21
says for Since By Man Came Death by man
came also the resurrection of the dead
so now how can an angel come by
man
possible Point Blank death is a state of
condition by Man Came Death let's see
who that man is go ahead for as in Adam
all die even so in Christ shall all be
made
alivee everybody that died that suffered
death that that died they they they had
taken on death that's not an Angel
that's a condition but go ahead and read
but every man in his own order Christ
the first fruits afterward they that are
Christ at his coming
go ahead then cometh the end when he
shall have delivered up the kingdom to
God even the father when he shall have
put down all Rule and all authority and
power go ahead for he must Reign till he
have put all enemies under his
feet The Last Enemy that he shall that
I'm sorry The Last Enemy that shall be
destroyed is death
and that's it because death is The Last
Enemy how why is death The Last Enemy
because when Jesus terminate death that
means stop people from dying there ain't
no enemies
left that's why you go to first uh the
Revelation 21st
chapter and and and let's go and read it
this is the last place Revelation 21 and
verse one okay
Revelation 21:1 says and I saw a new
Heaven and a new Earth for the first
Heaven and the first Earth were passed
away and there was no more
sea go ahead and I John saw the holy
city New Jerusalem coming down from God
out of Heaven prepared as a bride
adorned for her
husband go ahead and I heard a great
voice out of Heaven saying
behold the Tabernacle of God is with men
and he will dwell with them and they
shall be his people and God himself
shall be with them and be their
God uhuh and God shall wipe away all
tears from their eyes and there shall be
no more death neither sorrow nor crying
neither shall there be any more pain for
the former things are passed away
there should be no more death why
because Jesus terminated
death remember death was added the Lord
said if you eat of the tree of the
knowledge of Good and Evil that's the
day you going to die
right9 death in hell is not
uh Angel the condition and the word hell
comes from the word
shuel because in Psalms said that you
delivered my my uh uh uh uh one you
brought me up uh uh from the grave and
another one in Psalms that mentioned the
grave which is suel don't have we don't
want spend the whole night running this
one thing down death is when you die
it's all that
simple you want to know what the the
second death is let's go back to
Revelation 20th chapter
and this is the last place on this
Revelation chapter
20 uh let's
see or the end of that
chapter verse uh I want no I want to
show something else
here uh start at verse
5 okay Revelation 20 verse5 says but the
rest of the Dead live not again until
the thousand years were finished this is
the first
resurrection go ahead blessed and holy
is he that have part in the First
Resurrection on such the second death
have no power but they shall be Priests
of God and of Christ and shall reign
with him a thousand
years so now through it said the second
death have no power
right the second death is
oh let's
see he in Revelations
here he said
this verse uh
verse
14 read it and death and hell were cast
into the Lake of Fire this is the second
death okay so the second death
mean don't have that mean that you ain't
going to die you're going to live
forever now
if that was an
angel then he's more powerful than than
almost as power ful is God cuz he killed
all these people but the Lord killed all
these people death is a state of
condition it's not an angel everybody's
not living is dead and and the and the
word hell come from the word
shuel I don't have time to find it now
we don't want to spend the whole night
on
it so in other words Shel mean grave in
this particular
thing that's all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question there sister de let's take a
walk into new
territory yes we are now into tonight's
Q&A for Wednesday March the 12
2025 Janie doe asks will there be a
water park and companionship in the
Kingdom there be a water park and
companionship in the Kingdom plenty of
companionship brother Jerome what you
say
companionship yes yes
sir in in the um son Kingdom in
particular I'll just deal with the sun's
Kingdom in particular it's gonna be
plenty
water yeah and I'm G show you some
things that people can do in this water
okay you might call it a water park I
can't read that in the Bible but I'm
just going to show you some things that
they can do in the water okay so let's
go to Ezekiel
47 and we going to read verse
1-5 okay Ezekiel
47 veres 1-5
says afterward he brought me again unto
the door of the house and behold Waters
issued out from under the thres thres
threshold of the house Eastward for the
Forefront of the house stood toward the
East and the waters came down from under
from the right side of the house at the
south side of the altar okay stop right
there and this is during the the Lord
Jesus's Kingdom okay and water is going
to be issuing out from under the throne
in the house where the throne is which
is the temple and it's going to go out
and get deeper and deeper as it goes out
okay keep reading then brought he then
brought he me out of the way of the gate
northward and led me about the way
without unto the utter gate by the way
that lookth Eastward and behold there
ran out waters on the right
side and when the man
that go ahead keep reading it to five
and when the man that had the line in
his hand went forth Eastward he measured
a thousand cubits and he brought me
through the waters the waters were to
the ankles again he measured a thousand
and brought me through the waters the
waters were to the
knees again he measured a thousand and
brought me through the waters were to
the
loins afterward he measured a thousand
and it was a river that I could not pass
over for the waters were risen Waters to
swim in a river that could not be passed
over yeah you're gonna be able to swim
into this literal Waters that you can
actually swim in now if they gonna make
it a park I don't know you know but you
can swim in some water okay so now as
far as the companionship let's go to
Ezekiel 37 and we're going to read verse
21-2 okay Ezekiel 37 vers 21- 2 says and
say unto them thus sayeth the Lord God
behold I will take the children of
Israel from among the Heathen whether
they be gone and will gather them on
every side and bring them into their own
land and I will make them one nation and
the land upon the mountains of Israel
and one King shall be king to them all
and they shall be no more two Nations
neither shall they be divided into the
kingdoms anymore at all so once again
this is doing the Lord's Um Kingdom okay
you gonna have Flesh and Blood uh in
this Kingdom you also going to have
Spirit BS but the spirit BS not going to
be the ones having companionship
okay it's the flesh and blood during
this time go ahead neither shall they
defile themselves anymore with their
Idols nor with their detestable things
nor with any of their transgressions but
I will save them out of all their
Dwelling Places wherein they have sinned
and will cleanse them so they shall be
my people and I will be their God and
David said and David my servant shall be
king over them and they all shall have
one Shepherd they shall walk in my
judgments and observe my statutes and do
them and they shall dwell in the land
that I have given unto Jacob my servant
wherein your fathers have dwelt and they
shall dwell therein even they and their
children and their children's children
forever and my servant David shall be
the prince
forever okay so when the Lord back they
going to be having children they
children going to be having children
children and they ain't going to be
cohabitating freely too much while the
Lord here without being
married okay that's all I got on
it hope you're muted brother
Cornell Thank you for that brother hope
that answered their question as we move
on to our next one and this next
question I'm going to open it up to the
panel so all right next question Sai
amiru Israel asked in Revelation 7:
4-10 are the
144,000 alive in the tribulation or are
they dead and resurrected with the other
nations in verse 9 and
10 all right let's uh go to that
Revelation
7 but they got verse four here
yes Verses 4 through1 all right let's
pick it up at that four because we'll be
dealing with some people that'll be in
the eye of the storm during this Great
Tribulation but go ahead pick it up at
uh pick it up at three and read brother
go ahead okay saying hurt not the Earth
neither the sea nor the trees till we
have sealed the Servants of our God in
their
foreheads and I heard the number of them
which were sealed and there were
sealed
144,000 of the tribes of the children of
Israel of the tribe of Judah were sealed
12,000 of the tribe of Ruben were sealed
12,000 of the tribe of GAD were sealed
12,000 of the tribe of Asher were sealed
12,000 of the tribe of nepalm were
sealed TW seal 12,000 of the tribe of
Manasses were seal 12 12,000 of the
tribe of Simeon were seal 12,000 of the
tribe of Levi were seal
12,000 hey you don't need to do all that
reading you're eating up all the time
get down to verse n okay read it after
this I beheld and low a great multitude
which no man could number of all the
nations and kindreds and people and
tongues stood Before the Throne and
before the lamb clothed with white robes
and Palms in their hands
now the question was were these people
in the first resurrection did they say
that they said were they alive are the
144 alive in the tribulation or are they
dead and resurrected with the other
nations that they mention in verses 9
and 10 none of them was
resurrected let's back up to uh uh the
six uh chapter and see why we got all
this seiling in the first place 6 And1
12 Revelation 6
and12 and I behold when he had opened
the six seal and lo there was a great
earthquake and the sun became black as
sackcloth of hair and the moon became as
blood uhuh go ahead and and the stars of
Heaven fell into the Earth even as a fig
tree casteth her untimely figs when she
is shaken of A Mighty Wind
go ahead and the heaven departed as a
scroll when it is rolled together and
every mountain and Island were moved out
of their
places huh go ahead and the kings of the
earth and the great men and the rich men
and the chief captains and the Mighty
Men And every Bond Man and every free
man hid themselves in the dens and the
rocks of the mountains and said to the
mountains and rocks fall on us and hide
us from from the face of him that sth on
the throne and from the Wrath of the
lamb now the people have gone through
Great
Tribulation real hard times and you got
some people that was in that area that
survived it so now Jesus is getting
ready to Pro his wrath out but he don't
want to punish the same people
twice so
now he going to seal these people seven
and one
and after these things I saw four Angels
standing on the four corners of the
Earth holding the Four Winds of the
earth that the wind should not blow on
the earth nor on the sea nor on any
tree go ahead and I saw another Angel
ascending from the East having the Seal
of the Living God and he cried with a
loud voice to the four angels to whom it
was given to hurt the earth and the sea
saying hurt not the Earth neither the
sea nor the trees till we have sealed
the Servants of our God in their
foreheads now so now these are living
Flesh and Blood people Y and they uh uh
and they was not in the first
resurrection skip down to verse 13 and
let me show you what it says
here and one of the elders
answered saying unto me what are these
which are arrayed in white robes and
whence came
they and I said unto him sir thou
knowest and he said to me these are they
which came out of Great Tribulation and
have washed their robes and made them
white in the blood of the
Lamb the first thing is these people was
converted during the Great Tribulation
that's why he said it came out of Great
Tribulation they watched their R and the
blood of the Lamb these people were the
you know they was converted during the
Great
Tribulation but go ahead let's see what
it said about it go ahead therefore are
they Before the Throne of God and serve
him day and night in his Temple and he
that sth on the throne shall dwell among
them they they shall hunger no more
neither thirst anymore neither shall the
sun light on them nor any heat for the
lamb for the lamb which is in the midst
of the throne shall feed them and shall
lead them unto living Fountains of water
and God shall wipe away all tears from
their
eyes now you say going to lead them to
Fountain of Living Waters that mean
these people are not Immortals they was
not changed in the resurrection these
are first and blood Flesh and Blood
people now let's go into Isaiah the 49th
chapter
Isaiah
okay I think we're going to start this
about the E
verse okay uh Isaiah 49 verse 8 says
thus sayth the Lord in an acceptable
time have I heard thee and in a day of
salvation have I helped thee and I will
Preserve thee and give thee a covenant
of the people to establish the Earth to
cause to inherit the desolate
heritages go ahead that thou mayest say
to the prisoner go forth to them that
are in darkness show yourselves they
shall feed in the ways and their pastur
shall be in all high
places uhuh they shall not hunger nor
thirst neither shall the heat nor Sun
Smite them for he that ha Mercy on them
shall lead them even by the Springs of
water shall he guide them so these are
Flesh and Blood people these are the
same people that he's talking about in
Revelations so no they not they weren in
the first resurrection they were Flesh
and Blood people they was converted
during the Great Tribulation but still
they had to be
taught that's the end of
that all right hope that aned your
question there as we move on to our next
one moving on N Jones have two questions
one in Revelation chapter 7 we're in
chapter 7 again verses
5-8 is naming the tribes of
Israel that will be accounted for within
the 144,000 during the Great Tribulation
the tribe of Dan is not mentioned but
the tribe of
NASA is why and the second question is
where is the art of the
Covenant all right brother Julius what
you
say I'm going to answer the first the
last question first and then I'm going
to ask the guest caller to assist with
the first part of
that uh where's the where is the Arc of
what was it
Debbie where is the arc of the Covenant
let's go to Revelation the 11th
chapter Revelation 11th chapter brother
James
because we let the Bible tell you where
it's
at Revelation 11: 19 brother read it
when you get it and the temple of God
was opened in heaven and where in heaven
and go ahead what did John see and there
was seen in his Temple the Ark of his
Testament and there were Lightnings and
voices and thunderings and an earthquake
and great hell so the Ark of the
Covenant which is also called the Ark of
the Testament is up in heaven in the
temple of
God guest caller for that first part of
that
question all right and
the go
repeat all right the question is
chapter SE Revelation 7 5-8 is naming
the tribe of Israel that will be
accounted for within the 144,000 during
the Great Tribulation their question is
the tribe of Dan is not mentioned but
the tribe of manasse is
why because it was a type of 12 tribe
manasse eph and manasse are Joseph's
Sons yes sir
it should have been Joseph and
Dan all right and read that verse four
James just to back up what guest caller
said and I heard the number of them
which were sealed and there was sealed
144,000 of all the tribes of the of all
the tribes so nobody can nobody can be
missing no tribe can be missing it is
thank you guest caller a
typo all right we're going to leave it
right there we're going to move on to
our next question as time is a tiing yes
next question most love asks how do you
make the first resurrection do you have
to be dead already when Jesus come
back
no yes caller go
ahead 1 Thessalonians the 4th chapter
start reading at verse
13 okay ver 1 Thessalonians the 4th
chapter verse 13 said says but I would
not have you to be ignorant Brethren
concerning them which are asleep that ye
sorrow not even as others have no hope
no for we for we believe that Jesus died
and rose again even so them also which
sleep in Jesus will God bring with him
uhhuh for this we say unto you by the
word of the Lord that we which are alive
and remain until the coming of the Lord
shall not prevent them which are
asleep go ahead for the Lord himself
shall descend from heaven with the shout
and with the voice of the Archangel and
with the Trump of God and the dead in
Christ shall rise first
then then we which are alive shall
remain I'm sorry then we which are alive
and remain shall be caught up together
with them in the clouds to meet the Lord
in the air and so shall we ever be with
the Lord yes sir let you know that the
dead are going to be raised but you're
going to have some living that's going
to be changed and going to be in the
resurrection let's go to one other place
first Corinthians 15 and verse ver
51 1 Corinthians
15 and verse 51
says 51
says behold I show you a mystery we
shall not all sleep but we shall all be
changed and let so you have some living
people when Jesus come and they going to
be changed and they going to meet the
Lord in the air with the dead folks
that's going to be raised then
everybody's going to come back to this
earth that's all I have to
say yes be found keeping the
Commandments when he show
up all right that's correct we're going
to move on to our next question as time
is a
ticket next question Malik shur says I
know the other nations supposed to learn
from Israel but once they are learned is
it okay for for them to teach Israel or
the other
nations open to the
panel would somebody go and read where
after the Lord has go come back where
the je where the Gentiles say our
fathers hav heed
Li and somebody find it right
quick all right we are in search mode
for that right
now I think it's in Jeremiah jiah jiah
16 and 19 yes
sir Jeremiah
16 and 19
says oh Lord my strength and my Fortress
and my refuge in the day of Affliction
the Gentiles shall come unto thee from
the ends of the Earth and shall say
surely our fathers have inherited lies
vanity and things wherein there is no
profit
now now now how is it that they going to
teach
somebody and when the Lord come they
going to say to him our fathers have
inherited
lies that's at the last
day read the question again D I can't
believe I heard that question believe I
want to make right the yes the question
was I know the other nations supposed to
learn from Israel but once they are are
learned is it okay for them to teach
Israel or the other
nations the answer is no one other place
Isaiah the 2
chapter
okay start at verse one okay Isaiah 2
and verse one says the word that Isaiah
the son of Amos saw concerning Judah and
Jerusalem and it shall come to pass in
the last days that the mountain of the
Lord's house shall be established in the
top of the mountains and shall be
exalted above the hills and All Nations
shall flow unto
it and many people shall go and say Come
Ye and let us go up to the mountain of
the Lord to the house of God of to the
god to the house of the god of Jacob and
he will teach us his ways and we will
walk in his paths for out of Zion shall
go forth the law and the word of the
Lord from
Jerusalem so and that is the way it is
point
blank so now they can't
teach Israel they really can't teach
themselves because what happened in 7 ad
when Israel was taken
out all those Gentiles that was that
Paul had taught had not gone in the camp
ity nobody sold them nobody did nothing
to them why is it then that we have
people going to heaven and dead people
uh uh uh you know flying around how is
it that we have Easter and
Christmas so their lives they
inherit that's it so now this is the end
of it they at that time they going to
say our father inherited lies and then
the Nations going to say let's go up to
Jerusalem
so cu the law cuz they want to go and
and be taught isn't this what it say yep
the question to your answer is no don't
have to say all right so hope that
answered your question there sister
Deborah as we are approaching our last
question or two for the evening the next
one please yes next one Mark Ash asked
was the 120 years in Genesis 6 ver verse
three until the flood or man's lifespan
since Abraham Isaac and Jacob lived
Beyond 140 years in Genesis 47 verse
28 all right let's go to that um Genesis
and3 and let's read that and then sister
Deborah go over that question again and
then um we'll open it up to the
pound go ahead James
there you muted
James you
muted
okay and and Genesis 6 verse3 says and
the Lord said my spirit shall not always
strive with man for that he also is
flesh yet his days shall be 20 years and
the question pertaining to that script
de so they want to know was the 120
years in Genesis 6
verse3 and uh until the
flood or man's
lifespan since Abraham Isaac and Jacob
live beyond 140 years and then they give
47 verse 28
all right let's read Genesis
47 what you say 47 and what 28 verse
28 okay Genesis uh
47:28 says and Jacob lived in the land
of Egypt 17 years so the whole age of
Jacob was 100 14 and7
years well answer that question is God
say he going to cut it down to 120 but
he didn't tell you
when so now you can't even get to be
120 but he didn't say
when yep he cut it down later to 70 say
if you live by reason to 80s by reason
of strength but we got people living a
100 do God do whatever you want to
do but how many people you got nowadays
that live with 120
years I don't know
n me
right if they live beyond that just by
read like the guest caller said like the
scripture say Psalm 9 and10 by
reading God is merciful whom he will
be that's it when you get to be 80 years
old now people thank you
oh yep for sure God put cut it down 120
but he didn't it cut it down to 70 but
then God is God you look at the overall
more D younger than those these that are
Liv that they are
living
yep well that's all I have to say all
right sister de let's take one more
question and we're going to bring our
evening to a close all right uh uh
Jennifer Love ask if a group of women
get together to discuss previous lessons
and present our questions during Q&A are
we in error since no maale is
involved all right so a group of women
are getting together to discuss the
Q&A uh previous lessons and they present
uh their questions during a
Q&A are they in error since no male is
involved no guess guess caller what you
say I
don't no nope
not it shall be given
it it's okay for them to do a little
sharpening too
that's
correct Spirit up on his handmaids and
and his daughters
right see yep so no you're not in
violation and uh hey it's a good thing
to sharpen that iron never know who you
might be able to
edify all right sister Deborah time
check yes the time is
9:01 all right 9:01 we have ran out of
time and we want to thank everybody from
all around the world who joined us this
evening and we want to say if you
submitted a question and we didn't have
a chance to get to it please don't
resubmit that question sister Deborah
take it put it in rotation and we will
deal with that question next week so we
want to say to everybody that joined us
thank you and we say until we all come
together again be safe be blessed stay
prayed up and may the Lord have Mercy on
us all as brother James closes us
out Our Father which art in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our debts as we forgive
our debors and lead us not into
temptation but Deliver Us from Evil for
thine is the kingdom and the power and
the glory forever in Jesus name we pray